The Principality of Zeon
A gigantic space
citystate floating beyond the moon
Is dominated by
the Zabi royal family
Who are determined to control all of humanity
Girenz Abi
leader of
the Abi family
began his battle
with the Earth Federation
in order to force all of mankind to kneel before him
The White Base
which had managed to survive the Zeon attack
escaped from the
space colony side seven and descended to Earth
The young crew however have been forced to continue fighting one battle after another
And for Amuro
saying goodbye to his long lost mother was an even heavier burden
Time be still
I call this trick
victory to the principality
Get him
out of here
Get out
I don't need that
stupid bird around my zaku
I need ammo
Hey，Yell
yelling at the
pigeons won't get you far
leave it alone
This close to
the battlefront
and all I do is
scrape bird droppings off my zaku
Hey，come on
down now，Yell
we gotta talk
Alright
What is it？
Isn't the wreck
crew out here？
Yeah
it's gotta be
boring without any girls
You mean
the Federation's
mobile suit is out here？
You know Saul
the com guy，right？
He gets reports
through command
and I heard
it from him
Then does that
mean our unit is heading out pretty soon？
Dole，we're
just a patrol unit
So the last thing
they're gonna do is send us out to fight
Plus we got a
pretty nervous CO
and he's not
gonna want to start something
And so…
We've been thinking of hitting that Federation mobile suit
with just the
younger guys in our patrol
You really want
to hit that mobile suit？
And how many of
these things do we have to deal with？
Well，Yal
the commander
says it's okay for us
to take out the
enemy on our own
as long as we don'
t get them into any trouble
If all goes well
then they'll have
no choice but to send us home
Back to
civilization
where we'll
kick up our feet
and enjoy nice
clean
bugfree Zion
Yeah，but
what about…
There's only my
one Zaku in this entire unit
so what about
you guys，huh？
Hey，Saul
tell 'em the plan
okay？
So far
our adversary has
depended on one mobile suit
And it's not much
better than a prototype
The engine repair
will be completed by the crack of dawn
There's nothing
to worry about，Now
you were wanting
to ask me about something？
You're well aware
that we're not regular soldiers
So why are you
bothering to resupply us
And do all these
extensive repairs on White Base
Lieutenant？
The Federation
doesn't want to abandon the White Base
After everything
they've invested
And they do intend to send out a ranking officer
Who'll act as
your superior
However
there's a big
offensive being planned in Europe
Your small crew
has been winning tough battles
With no
commander this far
And I'm afraid
the Federation simply does not have
any officers
available for you right now
Lieutenant Matilda
is it
really that bad？
The Xeons are in
the same situation
And now that the White Base's primary mission is turning out to be data collection
You'll just have
to do the best you can
Data collection？
Right
we've discovered that amateurs tend to devise more interesting strategies than professionals
We can pick up any information on your battles from the memory on your computer
So
what you're saying is you ignore us on purpose so that we can be guinea pigs？
You don't like
being a guinea pig
do you
Ensign Bright？
Well，I haven't
received such orders
Me？
Ensign？
Yes，well，anyway
that's what
General Revel said
They'll notify
you of your new rank soon enough
They sure like
to jerk us around
If it wasn't for
General Revel intervening on your behalf
you would've been
courtmartialed long ago
Courtmartialed？
Yes
What is it，Amuro？
It's your
time to sleep
so why don't you
keep your schedule？
Sir
Soldier？
It's like Mr
Bride has told you
Sleep is an
important part of a pilot's job too
Yes，ma'am
I'll keep
that in mind
I don't
believe him
Is it really so criminal to have taken control of White Base and Gundam Lieutenant？
Well，is it？
Until
just recently
My good ensign
Bright Noah
So，where
did you go
Amuro？
The restroom
It's that way
Yeah，well
whatever，Frau
What is it？
Nothing
nothing，Amuro
Let's go，Haro
What was that？
Hey，have you
had your meal yet
Amuro？
Amuro
have you had
your meal yet？
No，no，not yet
We're going to
breach the ZM patrols
So I want you to
have Gundam ready on standby
all right？
Yes，sir
Sir
this is Lieutenant Matilda's flight path
And this one
here is ours
Mr， Bright
Both routes
are clear，Sir
Do you think we have any chance of making it through successfully？
I suppose it's
up to the Zeon
I'm sure I saw it
Something shining
on the port side
The Manovski particles are too dense for us to identify the object
So we've no
choice but to send out a flare
Lieutenant
There's no
patrol scheduled here
so be careful
No response
to the flare
Descend
we'll escape
using full combat speed
Prepare
antiaircraft guns
It's a
medea transport
travelling at
full combat speed
It doesn't seem
to be carrying a load
I bet they must
have unloaded near here
Yeah
maybe it resupplied the Trojan horse
That Chief Korn
was talking about
It's possible
Send out a flare
Right
Quick，get
the zaku ready
Right，Hey
tell the commander we're moving out immediately
My life
When I attack
them with the zaku
They'll automatically retaliate with their mobile suit
Tell Chief
Quarren to be ready to jump in
Right，Sergeant
Hey，wait up
Chief Quarren
Saul，hurry up
When the mobile
suit comes out
we'll follow the
plan we discussed yesterday
Don't forget that
we all go home if this works out
Saul
you ready？
Sir
Why are they
up so early？
That's
quarren for you
I see it
there's the
Medea transport
Return fire at
one o'clock now
Make a
hard descent
I'll bet that
fire is coming from Izuku
Skim right
over the enemy
That's pretty
fast for such a big transport vehicle
Hey，where is it？
I wish I had
lagoon support right now
What？
The container
's been hit
Doesn't matter
keep going
Laser analysis
Lemedia is
in combat
Matilda's
in trouble
Attention all crew
The Lemedia has
been snared by enemy patrol
White base will
provide support
Mr， Bright，it's me
Why don't we
launch Gundam？
Let's do
that instead
because White
base isn't prepped with supplies
Yes
but are you
up for it？
Are you sure？
Sir
I'm ready
to launch
Is that it？
I hope nothing
bad has happened to Miss Matilda
Oh no
it's the Federation's new mobile suit
Gundam， look，Yes
but he didn't
have to bother trying to help us
Let's escape from
here so this wasn't all a waste of his time
Right
Good luck to you
Miss Matilda
Please don't get
too out of hand
Amuro
Did I get him？
Hey，what's
that noise？
That's it？
How are they gonna attack Gundam with just machine guns？
There's
nothing wrong at all
why am I
shaking so bad？
Hey，you're
not getting away
Show
You shouldn't
have come out
Hide under
the trees now
don't get
hit from a bomb
Where are they？
我會捉到你，我會
阿姆羅，答我，阿姆羅，你哋毀咗扎古？
阿姆羅，你答我啦
The enemy
ships arrived
Fall back and
shoot at the bombs on the mobile suit
Go
Lousy pilot
Listen
All we have to do
is hit one of those bombs
And that mobile
suit is gone forever
You don't
know who I am
You think I'
m a weakling？
I'll show
you my power
My shield has
just been…it's…
it's been
blown apart
Yes，I see now
They've flown
around gunning and planted bombs on me
They're gonna…
No
there's one here
What？
How many of these
bombs did they plant on my mobile suit？
What's going on？
Amuro
They've planted
bombs all over Gundam
Bright
This isn't
a good spot
I'll move to the
clearing up ahead and check
Right，Roger that
get Omer
down there now
He's the
bomb expert
and he'll be able
to give us a hand here
So we have to sit
here and wait 30 minutes for our bombs to go off？
Just be patient
Never thought it'
d be so easy to plant bombs on that mobile suit
Wonder if their
crew can save the mobile suit in time
It'd be much better if it could be done by remote control
It'd definitely be kaboom
You bet
A regular
patrol unit like ours
doesn't get
supplied with stuff like that
Wonder if their experts can remove the bombs in under 30 minutes
There's five left
right？
We had six bombs
but there's one
that blew up the shield
I can't wait
I'm not really
sure what to do
But all I can tell you is that it's set to detonate in a very short period of time
Almero
can you tell us anything from the Xrays that might be of any use to us？
Well
it doesn't
really tell me a lot
This thin wire
here should work like a time fuse
and that'
s about it
If we tear off
the plastic explosive from the magnet
we'll set it off
Right，Omer？
Yeah，that's right
We've got no
choice but to take them off by hand
Alright then
I'm doing it，go
But this is my
responsibility
Please
let me do it
There's very
little time
so please
head for safety
I'll get on it
It looks like the
pilots removing the bombs
If they
have any sense
they should know those bombs are automatically set to explode in a short while
That pilot's
removing them？
There's 12
minutes left until it's all over
Is he really
serious about this？
It's incredible
but he's removed
two bombs already
He's got guts
or maybe he'
s just crazy
Is he on the
third one already？Well
it looks like they
've got the crane up
Eight minutes left
Will he make it？
Why are we just standing around watching instead of helping him out？
If we all pitch in
it'll get
done much quicker
They all might
explode any second now
We don't want to
sacrifice any more than absolutely necessary
And Amuro's the
one who's volunteered to do it
What are you？
Please，no，Bravo
Let go，Mira
you're a coward
just like the rest of them
You're all cowards
Say what you want
Frau Bo
Restraining
yourself is also a sign of bravery
We just can't allow you to sacrifice yourself along with Amuro
You've got
it all wrong
Why Amuro？
He's a pilot
Why can't I
do it instead？
That's not
the point， Frau
You'll never be
able to handle those bombs better than Amuro
But Mira，You're…
You're horrible
Won't he give up？
If these explode now
that's it
for Gundam
and me
He's got another
one or two yet？
Yeah，I think so
He sure is
persistent
What kind of
soldier would be this crazy？
They're on a timer
and we gotta
assume he knows that
So he must be
pretty brave to keep at it
Knowing they
could explode at any second
But let's recruit
him for our side
It's taking
a lot of time
Where'd he go？
Let's see
It looks like he
went around back
Yeah
he's running
out of time now
阿爾，它太遲了
阿爾…
阿爾，不
好嘅，所有嘅嘢都係要將
Gundam嘅手臂同腿抬高啲，接管橋樑
不，我哋要你哋停手
繼續待喺白色基地
Wait
that
should be good
One minute and
twenty seconds
I don't think
you can do it
Amrou，hurry
it's taking too long
Okay
Go for it，Kai
Alright，guys
I'm driving
one kilometer
Look
they removed them all
Just 18
seconds left
So much for going
back home to Zeon
I suppose we're not the only ones willing to risk our lives in this miserable war
Hey
what do you
think he's like？
That fool who
removed all those bombs？
Got any more？
Sure you bet
There's a
car coming
What？ Looks like
a civilian truck over there
It's a
station wagon
That's strange
in this
remote place
what are
they doing？
Hey，check this out
A Zeon
mobile suit？
I don't think so
Who are you men？
And what are you
doing way out here？
Well
we're just a bunch of guys who are from around this area
Now
that wouldn't be
a Federation mobile suit
would it？Hey
is the guy who's
wearing the cool white uniform there
the pilot of that
colossal looking mobile suit？
What's wrong？
Did you
hurt yourself
Mr， Pilot？
Don't look
so serious
Mr， Pilot
Keep up the fight
and make us all proud
soldier boy
Good luck，kid
Lucky guys
I envy people who
get to live on Earth
They're
so carefree
They planted the bombs
Mira，those
were the soldiers
Sure seems
that way to me
The Gallop and
Goof appear in the desert
Sailor is desperate to know the fate of Shara
and launches into
battle against Bright's orders
Her reckless
actions put the White Base in danger
as Amuro
attempts a rescue
Mobile Suit Gundam
Next episode：
Sailor's Agony
Who will survive？
阿姆羅，振り向かないで
宇宙の彼方に輝く星は
阿姆羅，お前の生まれたふるさとだ